YOGA PUTRA PRATAMA



Contact

Address:

Perumahan Margasari Regency Blok E No.15 Desa Margasari Kec. Karawang Timur Kab. Karawang Provinsi Jawa Barat M8JV+8P

Phone:

- +6285810078366
- +6285342144448

Email:

Kodok.bentung@gmail.com

Languages

Indonesia English

Summary

I have experience as a team leader delivery of PT Borwita Prima Citra Prima Karawang. Able to operate microsoft office, adept to computers software & hardware, printer ink, printer barcode zebra. Enough knowledge of warehouse workflow & admin logistic. I have a driving license A & C.

Highlights

- Employees management
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- Creative
- Innovative
- Service-focused

Experience

Team Leader Delivery - Dec 2018 to May 2021 **PT. Borwita Citra Prima**, Karawang

Credit Analysis – Sep 2016 to Dec 2019 **PT. Citra Santosa Finance**, Karawang

Technical Support – Jul 2014 to Apr 2016 **PT. Duta Kalingga Pratama**, Cikarang

Education

Bachelor of Science: Management Information - 2012

Bina Sarana Informatika, Karawang